Guide to the Rice University Art Gallery records, 1971-2017 UA 066
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Office / Exhibition files, 1989-2005
  - "Pleasurscape," January-February 2001 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - News clippings (general) (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - "Untitled (Series No. 2)," March 9-April 12, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Rice Student Art Exhibition, April-May 2001 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - "Pastor Collux" (Summer Window Series, 2001) (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - "One Saw; the Other Saw," 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - "Ikasu," November 8-December 9, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - "The Tourist Project, Lee Ming Wei," January 17-February 24, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - "The Precious Stone and Gold Factory," March 8-April 14, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - "All That: (Student Art Exhibition), April 26-May 11, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - "Gusty Winds May Exist," Summer 2002 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - "Samesation" (Ester Partegos), September 20-October 27, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - "Bamboo Roof" (Shigesu Bon), November 9- (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Kim Davenport correspondence, 2002 (Box 22A, Folder 1)
  - "True, False, Slightly Better" (Phoebe Washblin), January 23-February 23, 2003 (Box 22A, Folder 2)
  - "Exit, the 40th Rice Student Art Exhibition" April 24 –May 10, 2003 (Box 22A, Folder 3)
  - "Re-creation of Fort Discomfort" September 18- October 26, 2003 (Box 22A, Folder 4)
  - "Haze" November 6, -December 14, 2003 (Box 22A, Folder 5)
  - "Fort Discomfort"- Fall 2003 (Box 22A, Folder 6)
  - "Ackroyd" January 22-April 4, 2004 (Box 22A, Folder 7)
  - "Insider/Outsider" February 5-27, 2004 (Box 22A, Folder 8)
  - "Under the Radar" April 22- May 8, 2004 (Box 22A, Folder 9)
  - "Sam Ran Over Sand or Sand Ran Over Sam" September 16- October 31, 2004 (Box 22A, Folder 10)
  - "The Singing Posters" November 11, 2004- (Box 22A, Folder 11)
  - "The Subject as Object, on the Object as Subject" (Box 22A, Folder 12)
  - Eve Sussman "89 seconds at Alcazar", Jan-Feb., 2005
  - "Superabundant Atmosphere" Jacob Hashimoto March 17-April 17, 2005 (Box 22A, Folder 13)
  - "Output" Rice Student Art Exhibit 42, April 28-May 14, 2005 (Box 22A, Folder 14)
  - White Webb "Eminent Domain" Nov. 10 - Dec. 11, 2005 (Box 22A, Folder 15)
  - "Diane Landry" 2005 (Box 22A, Folder 16)
  - "Conversation" January 19 - March 5, 2006 (Box 22A, Folder 17)
  - "10th Anniversary" 2006 (Box 22A, Folder 18)
  - "Shine" Student Art Show, April 27 - May 13, 2006 (Box 22A, Folder 19)
  - "Light My Fire" Lisa Hoke May 19 - August 31, 2006 (Box 22A, Folder 20)
  - "Rip Curl Canyon" Sept. 21 - Oct. 29, 2006 (Box 22A, Folder 21)
  - "Big Landscape, Big West" John Cerney Nov. 9 - Dec. 10, 2006 (Box 22A, Folder 22)
- Series III: Office files addendum, 1972-1994
  - Friends notebook, 1990-91 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Friends membership and income, 1990-91 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Friends meeting minutes, agendas, correspondence, 1991-92 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Friends notebook, FY92 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Friends notebook, 1992-93 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Friends membership solicitation, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Friends Spring Reception, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - FSAG revised constitution (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - CACH grant 1989: "Messages from the South" catalog (Box 23)
  - TCA grant proposal 1989: "Contemporary Mexican Photography" (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - CACH grant budget 1989: "Contemporary Mexican Photography" (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - CACH TCA grants FY91: "West Coast Monotypes" (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - CACH TCA grants FY92: "Small-Scale Sculpture" (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - CACH collaboration grant FY93: Texas Folk Art (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - TCA grant FY93: "Contemporary Realist Watercolors" (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - CACH grant FY94: "The Mask in Contemporary Art" (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Card file of exhibitions, 1972 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Oversized exhibition posters (Box 24)
- Series IV: Exhibition print materials and curatorial files, 1995-2010
  - Leon Golub/Adrian Piper, 19 January-13 March, 1995
    - Correspondence, general (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, artist/gallery (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Financial (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Installation (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Lecture/travel-Piper (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Loan agreement-Golub (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Loan agreement-Piper (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Photographic (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Post-exhbition-Golub (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Post-exhibition-Piper (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Press (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Public relations (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Research-Golub (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Research-Piper (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Think Deeply Well, 20 March-21 April, 1995
    - Attie, Dotty (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Financial (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Installation (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Loan agreements (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Photographic (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Public relations and press (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Research (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - To the Point, Student Art Exhibition, 27 April-13 May, 1995
    - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Financial (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Installation (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Press (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Public relations (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Seductive Matter, 7 Sept-14 Oct., 1995
    - Condition reports (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Events (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - Financial (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - Graphics-announcement (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - Graphics-brochure (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - Installation (Box 26, Folder 33)
    - Insurance (Box 26, Folder 34)
    - Loan agreements (Box 26, Folder 35)
    - Paper from class (Box 26, Folder 36)
    - Press (Box 26, Folder 37)
    - Public relations (Box 26, Folder 38)
    - Ramljak, Suzanne; guest curator (Box 26, Folder 39)
    - Research (Box 26, Folder 40)
    - Shipping (Box 26, Folder 41)
    - Adams, Phoebe (Box 26, Folder 42)
    - Anderson, Patricia (Box 26, Folder 43)
    - Bowen, Nancy (Box 26, Folder 44)
    - Brookner, Jackie (Box 26, Folder 45)
    - Cemin, Saint Clair (Box 26, Folder 46)
    - Krauss, Alyssa D. (Box 26, Folder 47)
    - Lasher-Oakes, Heidi (Box 26, Folder 48)
    - O'Connor, Maureen (Box 26, Folder 49)
    - Rudel, Ross (Box 26, Folder 50)
    - Seborovski, Carole (Box 26, Folder 51)
    - Shuford, Carol (Box 26, Folder 52)
    - Simonds, Charles (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Y. David Chung, 27 Oct.-9 Dec., 1995
    - Condition reports (Box 26, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence (Box 26, Folder 55)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 26, Folder 56)
    - Event-Asia Circle (Box 26, Folder 57)
    - Event-lecture (Box 26, Folder 58)
    - Financial (Box 26, Folder 59)
    - Graphics (Box 26, Folder 60)
    - Installation (Box 26, Folder 61)
    - Insurance (Box 26, Folder 62)
    - Photographic (Box 26, Folder 63)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 26, Folder 64)
    - Press (Box 26, Folder 65)
    - Public relations (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Research (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Shipping (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Cybervato, 11 Nov.-30 Dec., 1995
    - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Financial (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Installation (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Loan agreement (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Photographic (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Press (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Public relations (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Research- MECA (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Research-articles (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Michael Shaughnessy, 26 Jan.-2 March, 1996
    - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Events (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Financial (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Graphics (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Installation (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Photographic (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Press (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Public relations (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Research (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Narrating the Self, 26 April-11 May, 1996
    - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Financial (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Graphics (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Public relations (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Research (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Special Events, 1995-96
    - Day Without Art-MFAH book (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Day Without Art-Short stories (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - AIDS Awareness Day (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Laura Claridge lecture on Tamara de Lempicka (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - Changing Perspectives (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - Waldo Bien lecture (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - Fotofest (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - House, Home, Homeland (Box 27, Envelope 36)
    - Andres Serravo lecture (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - Membership party (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Cancelled 1996
    - The Pull of Beauty (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - Fred Wilson
      - Campus contacts (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Catalog (Box 27, Folder 41)
      - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Financial (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - Graphics (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - Installation (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Photographic (Box 27, Folder 47)
      - Press (Box 27, Folder 48)
      - Public relations (Box 27, Folder 49)
      - Research (Box 27, Folder 50)
  - Fred Tomaselli, 27 Sept.-3 Nov., 1996
    - Checklist (Box 27, Folder 51)
    - Contracts (Box 27, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence (Box 27, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 27, Folder 54)
    - Financial (Box 27, Folder 55)
    - Graphics (Box 27, Folder 56)
    - Insurance (Box 27, Folder 57)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 27, Folder 58)
    - Press (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Research-artist (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Research-articles (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Research-shipping (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Eve Andree Laramee, 15 Nov.-15 Dec., 1996
    - Checklist (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Condition reports (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Financial (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Graphics (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Installation (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Insurance (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Press (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Research-articles (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Research-artist (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Shipping (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Sol LeWitt, 26 Jan.-13 April, 1997
    - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Emerson loan (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Events (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Events-Stern lecture (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Financial (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Food for Thought (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Graphics (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Installation-complex forms (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Installation-wall drawing (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Insurance (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Installation (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Installation-cinder blocks (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Photographic (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Press (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Research-articles (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Volunteers (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Karim Rashid, Pleasurscape, 25 Jan.-25 Feb., 2001
      - Catalog (Box 32, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 32, Folder 26)
      - Events-Food for Thought (Box 32, Folder 27)
      - Events-Straus/Ballou dinner (Box 32, Folder 28)
      - Financial (Box 32, Folder 29)
      - Graphics (Box 32, Folder 30)
      - Installation (Box 32, Folder 31)
      - Photographic (Box 32, Folder 32)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 32, Folder 33)
      - Press kits (Box 32, Folder 34)
      - Press (Box 32, Folder 35)
      - Research-articles (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - Art Matters, Student Art Exhibition, 25 April-10 May, 1997
    - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Financial (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Graphics (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Installation (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Martha Burgess, Manly on the Plaid, 9 Nov.-17 Dec., 2000
      - Catalog (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Financial (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Graphics (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - Installation (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Krazy Kat/Herriman (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Press (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - Research-articles (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - Research-artist's statement (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Research-biography (Box 32, Folder 22)
      - Research-previous exhibits (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Yayoi Kusama, Dots Obsession, 18 Sept.-2 Nov., 1997
    - Correspondence (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence-Mattress Factory (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Financial (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - Food for Thought (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Graphics (Box 28, Folder 47)
    - Graphics-guestbook (Box 28, Folder 48)
    - Installation (Box 28, Folder 49)
    - Insurance (Box 28, Folder 50)
    - Lectures (Box 28, Folder 51)
    - Loan agreement (Box 28, Folder 52)
    - Photographic (Box 28, Folder 53)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 28, Folder 54)
    - Press (Box 28, Folder 55)
    - Shipping (Box 28, Folder 56)
  - Charles Howard, To the Absent Friend, 18 Nov.-21 Dec., 1997
    - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Financial (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Graphics (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Insurance (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Installation (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Lecture (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Loan agreement (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Photographic (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Press (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Public relations (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Research-articles (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Research-Camfield (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Martorell, 8 Jan.-15 Feb., 1998
    - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Events (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Financial (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Graphics (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Installation (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Photographic (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Press (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Research (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - Shipping (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - Volunteers (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Gary Hill, Reflex Chamber, 27 Feb,-12 April, 1998
    - Bank Draft Brewing Co. (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Financial (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Fotofest (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Graphics (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Installation (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Press (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Programs-discussion (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - Programs-gallery talk (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Programs-group visit (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Research (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Shipping (Box 29, Folder 39)
    - Lee Mingwei, The Tourist Project, 17 Jan.-24 Feb., 2002
      - Catalog (Box 33, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 48)
      - Financial (Box 33, Folder 49)
      - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 50)
      - Installation (Box 33, Folder 51)
      - Photographic (Box 33, Folder 52)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 33, Folder 53)
      - Press kits (Box 33, Folder 54)
      - Press (Box 33, Folder 55)
      - Research (Box 33, Folder 56)
      - Research-CV (Box 33, Folder 57)
      - Research-Houston (Box 33, Folder 58)
      - Tour (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Collapse, Student Art Exhibition, 23 April-9 May, 1998
    - Awards (Box 29, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 41)
    - Financial (Box 29, Folder 42)
    - Graphics (Box 29, Folder 43)
    - Installation (Box 29, Folder 44)
    - Photographic (Box 29, Folder 45)
    - Press (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Exhibitions overview, 1998-99 (Box 29, Folder 47)
    - Stephen Keene, 10 Sept.-18 Oct., 1998
      - Correspondence (Box 29, Folder 48)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 29, Folder 49)
      - Financial (Box 29, Folder 50)
      - Installation (Box 29)
      - Photographic (Box 29, Folder 52)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 29, Folder 53)
      - Press (Box 29, Folder 54)
      - Programs: Painting symposium (Box 29, Folder 55)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-Ellen Gallagher (Box 29, Folder 56)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-Jeremy Gilbert-Rolfe (Box 29, Folder 57)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-Kerry Marshall (Box 29, Folder 58)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-Richard Schiff (Box 29, Folder 59)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-Barry Schwabsky (Box 29, Folder 60)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-Lisa Yuksavage (Box 29, Folder 61)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-Arthur Danto (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Programs: Painting symposium-David Carrier (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Programs: Food for Thought (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Programs: Museum District Day (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Programs: Group visits (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Research-articles (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Research-artist's statement (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Research-previous exhibits (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Nicole Eisenman, Behavior, 5 Nov.-13 Dec., 1998
      - Catalog (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Financial (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Graphics (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Installation (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Photographic (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Press (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Research-articles (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Research-biographical (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Research-previous exhibits (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Michael Petry, The History of the World, 21 Jan.-28 Feb., 1999
      - Catalog (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Grant proposal (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Graphics (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Installation (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Photographic (Box 30, Folder 26)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 30, Folder 27)
      - Press (Box 30, Folder 28)
      - Programs: Group visits (Box 30, Folder 29)
      - Programs: Installation symposium (Box 30, Folder 30)
      - Research-articles (Box 30, Folder 31)
      - Research-biographical (Box 30, Folder 32)
      - Research-previous announcements (Box 30, Folder 33)
      - Research-previous exhibits (Box 30, Folder 34)
      - Research-Stella Dobbins (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Jane Miller: 18 March-18 April, 1999
      - Catalog (Box 30, Folder 36)
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 37)
      - Financial (Box 30, Folder 38)
      - Graphics (Box 30, Folder 39)
      - Installation (Box 30, Folder 40)
      - Photographic (Box 30, Folder 41)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 30, Folder 42)
      - Press (Box 30, Folder 43)
      - Research (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Moving On: Student Art Exhibition, 29 April-15 May, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Barry McGee, Hoss, 16 Sept.-24 Oct., 1999
      - Catalog (Box 30, Folder 46)
      - Correspondence (Box 30, Folder 47)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 30, Folder 48)
      - Financial (Box 30, Folder 49)
      - Graphics (Box 30, Folder 50)
      - Installation (Box 30, Folder 51)
      - Kilgallen, Margaret (Box 30, Folder 52)
      - Opening (Box 30, Folder 53)
      - Photographic (Box 30, Folder 54)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 30, Folder 55)
      - Press (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Research-articles (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Research-previous exhibits (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Shout Outs, 4 Nov.-12 Dec. 1999
      - Catalog (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Education (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Financial (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Graphics (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Installation (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Post-exhibition (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Press (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - General artists information (notebook) (Box 31, Folder 12)
        - Bovasso, Nina (Box 31, Folder 13)
        - Buvoli, Luca (Box 31, Folder 14)
        - Cooper, Diana (Box 31, Folder 15)
        - DeLaVega, James (Box 31, Folder 16)
        - Marello, Matt (Box 31, Folder 17)
        - Mellyn, Sean (Box 31, Folder 18)
        - Morales, Arnaldo (Box 31, Folder 19)
        - Newman, Nurit (Box 31, Folder 20)
        - Scher, David (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Stephen Henclee, Superthrive, 20 Jan.-27 Feb, 2000
    - Catalog (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - CV (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Financial (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Graphics (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Installation (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Photographic (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Press (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Programs: Food for Thought (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Research-articles (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 31, Folder 34)
  - Clubs of Bamako, 9 March-16 April, 2000
    - Catalog (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Fotofest (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Graphics (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Installation (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Museum of Fine Arts, Houston (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Opening (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Photographic (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Press (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Promotion (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Program-lecture ideas (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Programs-Food for Thought (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Research-articles (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Research-biographical (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Research-Deitch exhibit (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Research-photos (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Research-sculptures (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - On the Verge, Student Art Exhibition, 27 April-12 May, 2001
      - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Handouts (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Press (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Check It Out, Student Art Exhibition, 27 April-13 May, 2000
    - Checklist (Box 31, Folder 52)
  - Wolfgang Winter/Berthold Horbelt, Kastenhaus, 21 Sept.-29 Oct., 2000
    - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Financial (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Funding (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Graphics (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Installation (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Photographic (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Press (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Programs (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Research-articles (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Martha Burgess, Manly on the Plaid, 9 Nov.-17 Dec., 2000
    - Catalog (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Financial (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Graphics (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Installation (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Krazy Kat/Herriman (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Press (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Research-articles (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Research-artist's statement (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Research-biography (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Celeste Boursier-Mougenot, 9 March--12 April, 2001
    - Catalog (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Financial (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Graphics (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Installation (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Photographic (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Post-exhibition (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Press (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Research-articles (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Research-previous exhibits (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - On the Verge, Student Art Exhibition, 27 April-12 May, 2001
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence-artist (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Graphics (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Handouts (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Press (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - James Cullinane, Pastor Collux, 8 June-8 Sept., 2001
    - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 6)